{
    "subject": "resource/Hermann_Schubert",
    "predicate": "ontology/birthPlace",
    "object": "resource/Province_of_Brandenburg",
    "human_readable": "Hermann Schubert was born in Province of Brandenburg.",
    "questions": [
        {
            "score": 0.9239820241928101,
            "question": "Where was Hermann Schubert born?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.9136731028556824,
            "question": "What was the political climate like in the Province of Brandenburg during Hermann Schubert's birth?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8734261989593506,
            "question": "Is there a connection between Hermann Schubert and other prominent figures from the Province of Brandenburg?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8462837338447571,
            "question": "What province is Hermann Schubert associated with?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8074178695678711,
            "question": "What were some common occupations or industries prevalent in the Province of Brandenburg during Hermann Schubert's time?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8035635352134705,
            "question": "Were there any notable historical events that occurred in the Province of Brandenburg during Hermann Schubert's lifetime?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6392077207565308,
            "question": "What is the Province of Brandenburg known for?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6301238536834717,
            "question": "Can you tell me more about Hermann Schubert's birthplace?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.45931360125541687,
            "question": "Is there any other information available about Hermann Schubert?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.4200473725795746,
            "question": "What might have influenced Hermann Schubert's life based on his birthplace?"
        }
    ],
    "google_pages": [
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Hermann Schubert was born in Province of Brandenburg.",
            "html": "dbpedia_4279_0.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Is there any other information available about Hermann Schubert?",
            "html": "dbpedia_4279_1.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Can you tell me more about Hermann Schubert's birthplace?",
            "html": "dbpedia_4279_2.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What is the Province of Brandenburg known for?",
            "html": "dbpedia_4279_3.html"
        }
    ],
    "selected_docs": [
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_4279_10.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_4279_17.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_4279_2.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_4279_20.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_4279_26.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_4279_32.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_4279_39.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_4279_4.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_4279_65.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_4279_7.txt"
        }
    ],
    "final_question": "Is true?",
    "responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": 0,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'no'}\n``` \n\n\n\n\nLet me know if you have any other triples you'd like to evaluate!"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": 0,
            "full_ans": "Here is the evaluation result:\n\n{\n  \"output\": \"no\"\n}\n\nThe reason for this answer is that none of the documents mention Hermann Schubert being born in the Province of Brandenburg. According to document 10, he was born in Potsdam, Germany (which is part of the Province of Brandenburg), but not within the province itself."
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "short_ans": 0,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'no'}\n```\n\nThe documents do not provide information to support the statement that \"Hermann Schubert was born in Province of Brandenburg.\" The first document mentions he was born on 28th August 1892 at Sillium in the county Marienburg, which is part of the province of Hannover. None of the documents mention Brandenburg or any direct connection to it regarding Hermann Schubert's birthplace."
        },
        "mistral": {
            "short_ans": 0,
            "full_ans": " {\"output\": \"no\"}"
        }
    },
    "need_tiebreaker": false,
    "tiebreakers_responses": {
        "qwen2.5:14b": {},
        "llama3.1:70b": {}
    },
    "final_decision": 0,
    "actual_decision": 1,
    "analysis": {
        "stratum": "Popular",
        "topic": "-"
    },
    "errors": {
        "mistral": {
            "reason": "Hermann Schubert, born on July 10, 1964, was not born in the Province of Brandenburg. According to the provided context information, he was born in Munich, which is in the state of Bavaria.",
            "category": 2
        },
        "gemma2": {
            "reason": "Hermann Schubert was born on 28th August 1892 at Sillium in the county Marienburg in the province of Hannover.",
            "category": 2
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "reason": "There is no mention of Hermann Schubert being born in the Province of Brandenburg, but there are mentions of him being born in other places such as Sillium (in the county Marienburg, province of Hannover), Munich, Berlin, and Potsdam.",
            "category": 2
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "reason": "The context provides birthplaces such as Sillium in the county Marienburg in the province of Hannover, Berlin, and Potsdam. There is no mention of Brandenburg as Hermann Schubert's province of birth.",
            "category": 2
        }
    }
}